It says yep Leon's top outdoor coffee something something so I want to learn this time right so I come to new chat and I say
Yes, I say
Gemini I
Speak English and I love French
but I have
No idea where to start right and
I'm going out in Leo
for a coffee and I want you to
Practice with me a conversation
That I'd have with the bartender, right or
Let's say barista now bar no what is bought in there over here now the barista right so I
Also open tools and this time I click guided learning so this is when it comes to education and using ai for learning new things
right so I click submit and
Let's see what we get
So it says set on excellent e-day getting set on excellent e-day getting ready for a coffee in Leo and
Yup in French you can politely ask for something by saying
Jovoutre
a
Jupant, right?
Yes, so I can continue this conversation. Yeah, it says barista says bonjour
Kesche Jovoutre
Hello, what can I get for you? How would you?
Greet me back and order an cafe. Yeah, so this is a conversation. This is happening
Actually, so I can continue the chat and I can say that okay
Let's say
Bonjour and espresso silver play
Didn't catch that
So let's just type it right. So I say Bonjour and espresso
silver play
Trebien you nail the greeting and the order
Using silver play perfectly. That's essential for being polite in a French cafe, right?
And the conversation goes on as you see so this is also the learning mode the guide
Learning mode, which is perfect when it comes to learning stuff which and can be perfect can be very useful